Today we will talk about Super Topper Plan.
Super Topper plans are basically those
plans which are low in price
and high in cover.  Meaning
more cover at a lower price.  So
what is its concept?  The concept is that there is a
deductible amount.  There is a small amount
that you have to bear first.
Your insurance cover is activated on top of that.
So there are super top up plans with deductible.
Now you
can also take super top up with the base policy.  Suppose
your base health insurance policy is already in force.  You
can take it with you.  Your
corporate cover is up and running.  Insurance is going on in some company.  On
top of that
you can buy your personal super topup.  Or
no cover going anywhere.  You may
want to take a super top-up policy with a deductible to reduce costs.   If you
want to understand Super Topup in detail then
its video is given below.  You can check.
So today we will compare the super top-ups
of five insurance companies so that you
can decide which super
top-up is best for you.  A disclaimer:
Please do your due diligence before starting the video.
Before taking any policy,
read the policy wording and read the brochure.  See your need.
Analyze your needs to see if this
product is right for you or not.
[MUSIC]
And a quick reminder.  If you have
n't subscribed to our channel yet, do so so that
you get the right information at
the right time.  Let's move on to the video.
Super Top Up Plus Comparison.  Here we are
comparing the super top-up plans of five companies.  The
first one is Neevapa Health
Recharge.  The second one is HDFC Arbo Medshur
Super Topup.  The third one is ICIC LBA Activate
Booster.  Fourth is Aitya Birla Super Top Up
Plan B and fifth is Tata AIG Micare
Plus Plan.  So, we will compare these plans
in detail, what are their features
, what are their eligibility criteria
, what are the differences and finally we will
also talk about the premiums.  So that you
can decide.  First let's talk about room
eligibility.  Eligibility Neema Bhupa
Health Recharge has a single private AC room.  There is
no room rent capping in HDFC Ergo MS Super Topup.  Actual
pay will be made on this.  ICICI Lombard Activate
Booster has a single private AC room.
No room rent capping in Aitya B Birla Super Top Up Plan B.  There is
no room rent capping minimum and
maximum entry age in Tata AIG medicar plus, so the minimum entry age is
18 years, in Neevapa health recharge
maximum is 65 years, in HDFC Ago Medi Super
Topup also you can enter from 18 to 65 years, the
policy will be life
long continued in the policy, if you have taken it then even if you are
70 or 80 years old, you can
run the policy.  ICI Lombd Activate
Booster Minimum Entry Age is 18 Years
Maximum 125 Years.  So you can understand
that you can enter this policy at any age.  The
minimum entry age for Aditya Birla Super Topper Plan B is 18
years.  The maximum age is 65 years.  In Tata AG
Medical Plus also 18 years and maximum
65 years.  We will move ahead with the edge of being dependent.
Dependent children can be added in Neevapa Health Recharge from 91 days.   You
can continue the policy for a maximum of 30 years.  You can enter into Medor Super Topup after 91 days
and continue the policy for a maximum period of 23 years.
91 Days to 30 Years in ICC Load Activated Booster.
In Aditya Birla Super Topper Plan B, you can continue this policy from 91 days to 25 years and in Tata IG
Medic Plus, you can continue this policy from 91 days to 25 years.
Now let
's talk about minimum and maximum sum
insured. How much sum insured
is available in your policy?  Neevapa Health Recharge
is available from Rs 5 lakh to Rs 95 lakh.
Options available from 5 lats to 95 lats.  Of
course with deductible, we will understand that also later.
HDFCO medishore Super Topup
offers coverage ranging from Rs 3 lakh to Rs 20 lakh.
Cover ranging from Rs 10 lakh to Rs 3 crore
is available in ICICI Low LMA Activate Booster.  Aditya Birla Super Topup Plan B
offers cover ranging from Rs 10 lakh to Rs 95 lakh.  Cover
of Rs 3 lakh to Rs 1 crore is also available in Tata Medicar Plus.
Now let's talk about
deductible.  Deductible, as I told you, is
an amount that you have to pay first
or this policy will work on that amount.  For
example, you received a claim of Rs 10 lakh.
For example, if we have taken a deductible of ₹1 lakh, then the
insurance company will not give any claim up to ₹1 lakh under
this policy.  Whether you
take it from your base policy, or
pay it from your corporate cover or bear it from your own pocket
, pay it yourself.
As soon as it crosses Rs 1 lakh, if the
deductible is Rs 1 lakh, then this policy will become active
and will give you the claim.  So whatever
deductible amount you have taken, that
threshold will have to be met first.
This policy will be active on that.  So higher the deductible
lower the premium.  You should understand that the
higher the deductible you take, the
lower your premium will be because the company knows
that you are
not going to claim up to that amount from this policy.  So you will see that
if you have a base policy then
you should take this of that amount on top of it,
suppose you have a base policy of 10 lakhs, then
take a deductible of 10 lakhs and take a super top
up on it, if you are going to take a super top up
or you have a corporate cover or you are
thinking that I will pay it from my pocket,
then go for a smaller deductible of
500 or 1 lakh, deductibles are also available
in some policies, take a smaller deductible,
so do not hesitate in paying that yourself and yes
this deductible is an annual aggregate, meaning as
I gave you an example, in a year there is a
claim of 10 lakhs and there is a deductible of 1 lakh.
As soon as Rs 1 lakh is crossed,
this policy will become active and Rs 1 lakh has to be crossed only once in a year.
Annual Aggregate Deductible once in a year, not repeatedly on every claim.
So the deductible option which
is available in Niva Health Recharge ranges from Rs 1 lakh to Rs
10 lakh.
2L to 5L option is available in HDFC Avo Medish Super Topup.
ICIC LBAD
Activate Booster is available in 3 lac to 20 lac
options.  So much higher deductible
options are also available.  If someone's
base is already running at Rs 20 lakh, then
you can take ICICI LBAD on that with 20 lakh
deductible.  So the premium will be very low.  The cover will
come in very large.  So you can see.   The
deductible options available in Aditya Birla Super Topper Plan B range from Rs 5 lakh to Rs
15 lakh.
Annual Aggregate Deductible: Deductible options of
2 lakhs, 3 lakhs, 5 lakhs, 10 lakhs, 15 lakhs
or 20 lakhs are also available in Tata IG Medical Plus.
So higher deductible options are available.
Tenure Policy Tenure.  So how many years of
policy can you take at once?  You know that if
you pay premium for more than one year
to the insurance company, there are two benefits.
Firstly, the insurance company
gives you a discount, multi-tenure
discount.  Secondly, you are locking your premium
for 2 years and 3 years, whatever the
term for which you are taking the policy.  So
in Neevapa Health Recharge, all three options one year, two year and
three year are available.
One year and two year options are available in HDFC Hergo Medish Super Topup.
One to three year options are available in ICIC LB Activate Booster.
One to three year policies are available in Aditya Birla Super Topup Plan B and
one to three year policies are also available in Tata AIG.
Now let's talk about the bonus.
Bonus is basically that if you are
not making any claim or you are
continuing with the same insurance company
then they give you some incentive.  So
in Neema Bhupa Health Recharge, if you
continue the policy then
you get loyalty addition which is 5% every
year maximum 50% will be given to you and this will be given
only on policies below Rs 25 lakh.  There is
no such bonus option in HDFCO Super Topup.  Same as ICICI Low LBA,
no bonus option is available in Aitya Birla also.  You get 50% no claim bonus in Tata LG.
Maximum 100% day
care procedures.  So day care procedures are
also covered in your policy.  These are
procedures where
you do not need 24-hour hospitalization.
You go in the morning and get discharged in the evening.
So in Niapa Health Recharge all
day care procedures are covered up to sum
assured.  All day care procedures are also covered in HDFC ao medishore Super Topup.
All procedures are also covered in your ICICI LBD
up to the sum insured.  Aditya Birla
Super Topup Plan B lists 586 day
care procedures that you can claim.
Similarly, Tata AIG also lists
over 540 day care procedures that you can
cover in the policy.  Home care
treatment.  So home care treatment is
not covered in Neevapa Health Recharge.  HDFC
categories cover up to sub insured.  IC
LMA is also covered in Activate Booster.  5%
off annual sub insured.  The maximum
cover will be up to ₹5 lakh.  Aditya Birla
Super Top Plan covers up to
₹50,000 Tata AIG Medic Plus covers
up to sum insured.  Now let's talk about
domiciliary treatment.  Domiciliary treatment is
that treatment where you
are hospitalized at home because there is
no space in the hospital or the patient is critical.
Cannot go to the hospital.
Your domiciliary hospitalization
is covered with Neevapa Health Recharge.  Not covered in HDFC Ergo.
Rest of your ICC Low LMA Activate Booster
is also covered in Aditya Birla Super Topper Plan and Tata IG Med Plus.  Ayush
Hospitalization is covered in Ayush Niva BP Health
Recharge.
AYUSH hospitalization is not covered under HDFC Ergo.
ICICI is covered in Super Topup,
Aditya Birla in Low LMA Activate Booster and Tata
in AIG.  So the
cost of organ transplant is covered up to
harvesting.  It is covered in all the plans.
Harvesting cost up to sum
insured.  Refill benefit.  Refill benefit is available
where your sum insured is
exhausted.  So the insurance company
refills your sum insured again.
So because you understand that there are
policies with higher sum assured, there is top up.
So in most of the policies you will
not get refill benefit.  It will be available only
in Tata IG Medic Plus and that too
for unrelated illnesses.  For which he has already been
hospitalized.  For that matter,
refill benefit cannot be claimed from restore benefit.  If there is an
unrelated illness, it will be
restored.  Emergency Road
Ambulance hospitalization will be provided at ₹1500 in Neempa Health Recharge.
HDFC Ago M
is not covered under Meshore Super Topup.  ICIC
LBAD Activist Booster is covered up
to sum insured.  In Aditya Birla Super Topup
Plan, if you are going to a network provider
where there is a Pay Cashless network then
S Pay Actual is covered.  If you are
going to a non-network hospital, then hospitalization will be provided only at ₹5,000.
Hospitalization at Tata AIG Medic Plus will cover ambulance expenses up to ₹1,000.
Emergency Air Ambulance
is not covered under Neevapa Health Recharge.  HDFC Bank
is also not covered under AoShor Super Topup.  ICC LBD can be
added with a rider add-on
which you can choose by paying extra premium.
Same can be added to Aditya Birla Super Top Up
Plan B through rider.
Emergency air ambulance is not covered in Tata IG.
Annual health checkup.  So
annual health checkup is
not available in Nima Bupa Health recharge.
Annual health checkup is also not available in HDFC Agar Medicio Super Topup.
Your ICIC LBAD
Activate Booster Annual Health Checkup is
not available in Plan A.  You
can add a rider to Plan B and the cashless amount will be
up to ₹5,000. Not covered in Aditya Birla.
1% of base sum
assured maximum ₹10,000 in Tata AIG.  This will be
given only on a block of two claim free years.  If you do
not claim for two years, then you
can claim this annual health checkup.  Wellness
Benefits.  So the wellness benefits are basically
that your step activity
counts daily.  On that basis you are
given discount on renewal.  So this
benefit is available only in ICICI Lo LBA
where pay wellness benefits will be given up
to 30% or you will have to download IL Tech Care app to
avail this benefit.
Then there are pre and post
hospitalization expenses.  This means that you can get reimbursed the
expenses before going to the hospital and
also the expenses after coming home from the hospital.
Neevapa Health Recharge has 60
days and 90 days.  60 days free and 90
days post.  HDFC Ergo Medisure Super
Topup is 30 days free and 60 days
valid.  Plan A of ICC LBA has 90 days
free and 180 days post.  And in plan B there
is 60 days free and 90 days post 90 days.
Aditya Birla plan has 30 days
free and 60 days post.  And in your Tata
AIG Medicare Plus plan, you can get reimbursed 60 days pre-
hospitalization expenses and 90 days
post-hospitalization expenses.  Then comes
e-
consultation Unlimited tele e-consultation
is available in your Nivapa Health recharge
HDFC Ergo Super Topup
E-consultation is not available in Medis Super Topup.
You can add unlimited e-consultations to the ICIC LMA Activate Booster
by paying an
additional premium.  Not available in Aditya Birla
and available in Tata LG Medic Plus
and
you can also take eMedical Opinion for specific illness.  Non
Payable Items So non payable items are
not covered in Neevapa Health Recharge.  HDFC
Ergo Medisor is also not covered under Super Topper.
You can add a rider to ICICI LAD called
Claim Protector to cover non-payable
items.  Not covered in Aditya Birla.
And it is covered in Tata IG plan
, it is inbuilt.  So non payable
items are inbuilt.  The consumable items
we call PP kits, masks, gloves are
covered in your policy.  Inbuilt.
OPD cover.  So OPD cover
is not available in NIVPA health recharge.  HDFC Agar
Medices is also not available in Super Topup.
In ICICI LBA you can add Be Fit rider
for OPD coverage.
OPD cover is also not available in Aditya Birla and Tata Ah.
Comments There are no comments in Neema BP Health Recharge.
Meaning the entire claim will be
paid by the insurance company only.  In HDFC Ago,
as soon as you cross 80, you have to pay 10%
on each and every claim.  There is
no copayment in ICICI LBAD.  There
is no copayment in Aditya Birla and there is
no copayment in Tata IG also.  So next is
modern treatments and robotic surgeries.
Modern treatments Robotic Surgeries will be covered at Neema Buba Health Recharge
with some submissions.  You can see this on your screen.
Treatments
are submitted.  Deep Brain Stimulation: The cost of this is Rs 5 lakh.
Immunotherapy will be given for Rs 5 lakh.
Robotic surgeries will be given for Rs 2.5 lakh.
So it is mentioned that this is it and
pre and post hospitalization is also included in this.
HDFC Ergo Medisure Super
Topup covers modern treatments as per
actuals.  Other plans like ICICI
Lo Lambar, Aitya Blend, Tata IG also
cover modern treatments as per
actuals.  If we talk about premium at slab, then the
premium at slab in all the plans is
five years.  The
premium increases on the 5 year slab.  Maternity
Expenses: Maternity expenses are
not covered in any of these five plans.  Then covers
global coverage.  So global coverage is
not available in Neevapa Health Recharge.  HDFC
and that is not even in Medis Super Topup.
Not even in ICICI.  Not in Aditya Birla.
But there is a rider available in Tata AIG
through which you can add global cover.  You
can also get treatment outside India through this policy.
Now let's talk about waiting periods,
what are waiting periods?  The initial waiting
period is 30 days in all five policies.
You cannot take plant hospitalization for the first 30 days.  Then comes
slow growing illness waiting period.
Meaning, some diseases which are
not covered for some time.  Things like stone,
cataract, hernia, piles, fibroids,
knee replacement will not be covered for two years.
Third is pre-existing
diseases waiting period.  Will there be a
waiting period for those who already have diseases
?  Pre-existing diseases will be
covered in Neevapa Health Recharge after 36 months.
HDFC Ago Medi Super Topup also has benefits
after 36 months.  Aitya Birla also has
36 months.  Tata EIG also has a waiting period of 36 months and
ICICI LBD Activate Booster also has a
waiting period of 36 months depending on pre-existing
conditions.  Now let's talk about optional
riders, whether there are optional riders that
you can add to your policy.  First of all,
Neema Health Recharge has Personal
Accidental Cover through which you can add cover for Accidental Death,
Accidental Permanent Total Disability,
Accidental Permanent Partial Disability
by paying
additional premium.  This cover is available up to 50 lakhs.
CI is covered.  A
lump sum payout is available for critical illness.  If any
critical illness is diagnosed.  There
is a list of 20 illnesses that you can cover
through the rider.  So CI cover is available up
to 10 lakhs and the waiting period is 90 days.  There are
no riders available with HDFC Argo Medi Super Topup.  Let's talk about the riders of ICIC LAD Activate
Booster.   The
first rider is Jump Start.  So ICC LAD
Activate Booster is basically a super
top up but it is working like the base policy,
if you see then
because there are all the riders in it, all the
types of riders that are there in your base policy
like ICC Lomard
is available in Elevate, so all those riders
are available here, the first one is Jump Start, you have to get A B
C D covered from day one which is
Asthma BP Cholesterol Diabetes then you
can take Jump Start.  Second B Fit
Rider which is your OPD Rider.  Third is
domestic air ambulance which I told you
you can add through rider which is
not available in other policies.  Fourth
is Claim Protector to cover your consumables.
Fifth is inflation
protector.  You can increase your sum assured
every year by 56% according to inflation.  So you can
also add inflation protector.
Health checkup.  There is a rider for annual health checkup.
You can add if you
need annual health checkup every year.  Dependent
Accommodation Benefit.  This policy can be
taken only at inception.  Guaranteed reduction of
deductible.  If you want your
deductible to keep getting reduced by 10% each year
up to a maximum of 50%, even if there is a claim,
this reduction will continue year on year, you
can also take this rider.  You
can take the rider of e-consultation.  You can take the rider of Nursing at Home.
Compassionate Visit has a
rider.  Durable Medical Equipment
Cover.  Waiting period reduction for PEDs.
You can also reduce the waiting period.
You can bring down the P period for specific illness from 24 months to
12 months.  There is a room modifier
option.  Meaning you don't want a single room.   If
you want any room category or want to
take it on twin sharing, then all those
options are available.  Premium will be
charged accordingly.  Network Advantage which is a
Preferred Partner Network Discount.
You say that this is the cashless list
of ICICI LBA, in which there are some preferred
hospitals which the insurance
company is preferring, which is being called
network advantage.  If you go to those hospitals
and take the list, you
get a discount of 10%.  But if you
go beyond that hospital, there is
also a co-payment of 20%.  This is called Preferred Partner
Network.  Its detailed video
is also available on our channel.  Please do refer,
I am giving its link below.  The Tata AG
Medic Plus has the global cover rider
available which we were talking about.  If you
want global coverage then you can take that rider.
Lastly, we will talk about
premiums.  So, you might want to know the premiums and how much
premium is charged for which policy.  Here
we have tried to keep similar sum assured
and similar deduct so that there is an
apple to apple comparison.  So
in Nivapa recharge, I have taken
family here.  Family size is three 35 31
and four and premium is charged for zone one.
Delhi has a premium.  Sum assured
is Rs. 95 lakh with Rs. 5 lakh deductible.  If
we are taking a family floater cover of 95 lakhs
for super top up and with 5 lakh deductible
then the premium will be Rs 5483.  If you are taking a policy of Rs 90 lakh
and there is a deductible of Rs 10 lakh
then the premium is Rs 1493.  Similarly,
if we take HDFC Ago Medshur Super Topup
because the maximum sum assured available is
20 lakhs, then if I compare 20 lakhs with 5
lakh deductible, its
premium is coming out to be Rs. 4543. Then comes ICICI
LBD Activate Booster, there 95 lakhs with 5
lakh deductible, the premium of Plan A is Rs. 9145, the
premium of Plan B is Rs. 9085. We had talked a little about
Plan A and Plan B in the video above.
If we are taking sum assured of Rs.
90 lakhs with 10 lakh deductible,
then the premium of Plan A is Rs. 3756, that of
Plan B is Rs. 3730. Then let's talk about
Aditya Birla, Aditya Birla 95 lakhs
with 5 lakhs deductible, that is the premium, that is Rs.
9933 and 90 lakhs with 10 lakhs deductible is Rs.
5726.
Your Tata IG Micare Plus 1 crore
service shot is available, so 1 crore with  5 lac
deductible is 9900 and 1 crore with 10 lac
deductible is 7200 so you can see
how comfortable you are in taking the deductible
accordingly you can calculate your premium and
choose the policy again again a
disclaimer if you want to take super topper policy then do
your due deletion.   Don't
forget to check out the policy wording brochure.  If you
want to connect with our team then the
contact number is given.  You can fill out Google Forms.
Our team will reach out to you
and help you completely in policy buying and
further after sales service as well.  So this is what
I wanted to tell you.
I have shared with you the comparison of super top up policies.
If you found it useful then don't forget to
share it with your friends and family.
And before we go, a quick reminder,
if you haven't subscribed to our channel yet, please do so.
So that you get the right
infection at the right time.  See you
in the next video.  Till then stay safe.  Take care.
Bye-bye.
[music]